A magical musical treat for the dreamer in all of us.
A Cinderella Story: If the Shoe Fits is a comedy, family,
fantasy film directed by Michelle Johnston.
A contemporary musical version of the classic Cinderella story in which the servant step
daughter hope to compete in a musical competition for a famous pop star.
Tessa Golden, played by Sofia Carson.
Reed West, played by Thomas Law.
Divine, played by Jennifer Tilly.
Olympia, played by Jazzara Jaslyn.
Georgie, played by Nicole Fortuin.
Athena, played by Amy Louise Wilson.
A Cinderella Story: If the Shoe Fits is a 2016 American musical teen comedy directed by Michelle
Johnston (in her directorial debut) and starring Sofia Carson, Thomas Law and Jennifer Tilly.
It is the fourth installment in the A Cinderella Story series.
The film was released digitally on August 2,
2016, and on DVD on August 16, 2016.
It premiered on Freeform on November 27, 2016 with
1.11 million viewers tuning in.
It also aired on Disney Channel on January 16, 2017 and
was watched by 2.13 million viewers.
It was followed by A Cinderella Story: Christmas Wish in 2019.
The film explores themes of dance, dancer, fairy tale, musical, celebrity.
The tone is lighthearted.